[{
	"id": 1,
	"botMessage": "Hi.. Welcome to Techupindia Bot",
	"botMessageType": "dialog",
	"nextResponse": 2,
	"retryPrompt" : "Please select correct option"
},{
	"id": 2,
	"botMessage": "Please enter your name(eg : firstname lastname)",
	"botMessageType": "text",
	"userMessageType": "text",
	"nextResponse": 3,
	"retryPrompt" : "Please select correct option"
},{
	"id": 3,
	"botMessage": "Please enter your Phone number(eg: 19876356728)",
	"botMessageType": "text",
	"userMessageType": "number",
	"nextResponse": 4,
	"retryPrompt" : "Please select correct option"
},{
	"id": 4,
	"botMessage": "Please enter your email id (eg:abc.@gmail.com)",
	"botMessageType": "text",
	"userMessageType": "mail",
	"nextResponse": 5,
	"retryPrompt" : "Please select correct option"
},{  
    "id": 5,
    "botMessage": "Please select from below?",
    "botMessageType": "choice",
    "choice": [{
      "option": "Students",
      "nextResponse": 6
    }, {
      "option": "Teachers",
      "nextResponse": 7
    },{
      "option": "Olympiad",
      "nextResponse": 8
    },{
      "option": "About Techupindia",
      "nextResponse": 9
    }],
    "userMessageType": "text",
    "retryPrompt": "Please select correct option"
  },{
	"id": 6,
	"botMessage": "Students",
	"botMessageType": "autocomplete",
	"userMessageType": "autocomplete",
	"nextResponse": 10,
	"retryPrompt" : "Please select correct option"
},{
	"id": 7,
	"botMessage": "Teachers",
	"botMessageType": "autocomplete",
	"userMessageType": "autocomplete",
	"nextResponse": 10,
	"retryPrompt" : "Please select correct option"
},{
	"id": 8,
	"botMessage": "Olympiad",
	"botMessageType": "autocomplete",
	"userMessageType": "autocomplete",
	"nextResponse": 10,
	"retryPrompt" : "Please select correct option"
},{
	"id": 9,
	"botMessage": "About Techupindia",
	"botMessageType": "autocomplete",
	"userMessageType": "autocomplete",
	"nextResponse": 10,
	"retryPrompt" : "Please select correct option"
},{  
    "id": 10,
    "botMessage": "What you want to do next?",
    "botMessageType": "choice",
    "choice": [{
      "option": "Have any other question",
      "nextResponse": 5
    }, {
      "option": "Want to exit",
      "nextResponse": 11
    }],
    "userMessageType": "text",
    "retryPrompt": "Please select correct option"
  },{
	"id":11,
	"botMessage": "Thanks .It was nyc to talk to you thanks",
	"botMessageType": "dialog"
}]
